communityofsweden.com 2011-11-12

# 

## Privacy

## 1\. General

### 1.1

VisitSweden will protect any personal data that VisitSweden obtains from you. Personal data is all kinds of information that directly or indirectly may be referable to a natural person who is alive, e.g. name, postal address, e-mail address and phone number. VisitSweden is committed to process your personal data in accordance with the principles herein and applicable law.

### 1.2

VisitSweden must be provided with personal data in order to create a User account. You agree that personal data may be processed by VisitSweden in accordance with this Privacy Policy, as in force from time to time. The personal data you provide must be accurate, complete and up to date. Do not provide any personal data to VisitSweden if you do not agree to this Privacy policy. VisitSweden reserves the right not to provide you certain products or services if you do not accept this Privacy Policy. You are never obliged to provide VisitSweden with personal data.

### 1.3

Please read this Privacy Policy as well as the User terms each time you intend to provide VisitSweden with personal data. The Privacy Policy may at any time and without notice be changed by VisitSweden. VisitSweden will change the Privacy Policy in order to keep it compliant with applicable law.

### 1.4

Depending the issue in question, VisitSweden or any of its subsidiaries is in control of the personal data. If you have any questions concerning VisitSweden’s processing of your personal data or this Privacy Policy, please contact us on the contact email address provided on the Website.

### 1.5

Hereinafter “Website” shall mean VisitSweden’s website www.VisitSweden.se and any sub-sites hereof, published and maintained by VisitSweden, or its subsidiaries.

## 2 Use of personal data

### 2.1

Without limitation, your personal data provided to VisitSweden may be used for the following purposes; provide to you requested products and services; attend to VisitSweden’s agreed obligations and rights towards you; process payments; administration; internal analysis to improve or more effectively tailor VisitSweden’s Website, business or offerings generally; allow you access to agreed products and services; direct marketing; any other purpose you have agreed on or which is allowed under applicable law. If any other purposes are stated on any relevant part of the Website, your personal data may also be processed for such purposes. Also, for the above purposes other information collected from you or third parties may be combined with your personal data.

## 3 Disclosure and transfer of personal data

### 3.1

Personal data may be transferred to VisitSweden’s business partners within or outside the EU/EEA for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. If any of the recipients reside in a country which has no adequate legal protection for personal data, VisitSweden will take reasonable measures in order to make the recipient adopt the principles stated herein.

## 4 Rectification and destruction of personal data

### 4.1

After the personal data is no longer required by VisitSweden for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or after it has come to VisitSweden’s knowledge that the personal data is inaccurate VisitSweden will make reasonable efforts to rectify, block, erase or de-identify such personal data within a reasonable time.

### 4.2

In accordance with applicable law, you are at any time entitled to require VisitSweden to rectify, erase or block your personal data. please contact us on the contact email address provided on the Website for such request.

### 4.3

According to applicable law you may receive information about your personal data processed by VisitSweden. Such request shall be in writing.

## 5 Security

### 5.1

Unauthorized access to personal data may occur and VisitSweden cannot guarantee otherwise. Through the implementation of appropriate technical and organizational measures VisitSweden is however as far as reasonable possible dedicated to maintain the security of personal data and preventing unauthorized access.
